[
  {
    "type": "intro",
    "pretext": "Awesome! You’ve learned about dakuten (゛) and handakuten (゜) and what happens when you add a marker to the hiragana characters of “K,” “S,” and “T.” Let’s review:"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "G",
    "options": ["Ga - が", "Gi – ぎ", "Gu – ぐ", "Ge – げ", "Go – ご"]
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "Z",
    "options": ["Za – ざ", "Ji – じ", "Zu – ず", "Ze – ぜ", "Zo – ぞ"]
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "D",
    "options": ["Da – だ", "Dji – ぢ", "Dzu – づ ", "De – で", "Do – ど"]
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "Ga and Gi",
    "options": ["ご and ど", "が and ぎ", "ず and ぞ", "が and じ"],
    "answer": "が and ぎ"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "Za and Zu",
    "options": ["ぜ＆ざ", "が and だ", "ざ and ず", "ぜand ぎ"],
    "answer": "ざ and ず"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "De and Do",
    "options": ["で and ど", "ぢ and だ", "ご and ず", "ず and で"],
    "answer": "で and ど"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "Go and Ji",
    "options": ["ぜand ぎ", "ず and で", "が and じ", "ご and じ"],
    "answer": "ご and じ"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "Da and Dzu",
    "options": ["ご and ど", "だ and づ", "ず and で", "ご and ず"],
    "answer": "だ and づ"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "Gu and Ze",
    "options": ["ぐ and ぜ", "ぜ＆ざ", "ご and ど", "が and だ"],
    "answer": "ぐ and ぜ"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "Ge",
    "options": ["ぎ", "ご", "げ", "ぐ"],
    "answer": "げ"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "Zo",
    "options": ["ぞ", "ざ", "ず", "ぜ"],
    "answer": "ぞ"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": " Dji",
    "options": ["ど", "で", "ぢ", "だ"],
    "answer": "ぢ"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "Hiragana",
    "options": ["ひらがな", "みず", "だんせい", "くちびる"],
    "answer": "ひらがな"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "Mizu",
    "options": ["くま", "みず", "にじ", "ちず"],
    "answer": "みず"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "Denwa",
    "options": ["くちびる", "でんわ", "だんせい", "みず"],
    "answer": "でんわ"
  }
]